The next thing we're going to do is make it so our player character can actually fire and spawn these
apples.
If we go to edit and go product settings, we're going to add a new button, and when we press this
button, we're going to spawn our projectiles.
So if I go to input and go add new action mapping and I'll call this spawn projectile.
And I'm going to assign this to the key.
I'll close this if we just open this up and go over to the viewport and go ad and look for a scene.
Now just cool this ah apple spline point.
Just select it and move it to where you want the apple to spawn some.
Place it around my character's hands.
Then we go back to the event graph.
Right click and look for the spawn projectile.
Bun.
And when we press this, we're going to drag up here and look for you once.
And then we'll go pay for spawn actor from pass.
The actor we're going to spawn is going to be the apple.
And where we're going to spoon this apple if we just right click on the Spawn transform, split the
structure pin and then drag in our apple spawn.
And we just want to get the world location of this object and hook it up to location.
Pull the rotation just right click and we'll get actor rotation and then hook this up here.
The drug.
I look forward to dealing.
And just right click and permit this terrible and just pull this all.
Reset time.
And just go compile.
You can customize the value here.
I'm going to make it to my player can spawn projectiles every 0.5 seconds.
And then we just drag them completed over to the reset or double click here.
Just make everything a bit tidier.
And now I go compile, close this, and I'm going to move my to here.
So if I go play and I'm crazy, I spawn an apple and it damages the scanner.
It looks like I signed the dashboard into Z, so let me change that.
Okay.
Whoops.
Looks like there's an error.
So it looks like the skeleton is struggling to find the damage causer.
Okay.
Yeah.
So if you remember in the skeleton, we set up this damage cause of reference.
And if I go back to my apple projectile, I've not set it at the damage causer.
So just drag up here and look for self.
That way it's going to knows what's damaging it when it's hit by the apple.
We can just compile this, close this and then if we go back to our product settings.
And back to the input.
Let's make the spawn product outside the X key.
Okay.
So I go close this, go play, and I shoot apples at my skeleton.
They get damaged.
Nice.